Contact

ebstorrs@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/elainestorrs-52468149 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Healthcare Management
Patient Safety
Healthcare

Certifications

IHI Open School Basic Certificate in Quality & Safety

Honors-Awards

Sigma Theta Tau International-Nursing Honor Society

Golden Key International Honor Society

Elaine Storrs

Western Division CNO & CNO North Colorado Medical Center at Banner Health

Greater Denver Area

Summary

Experienced Chief Nursing Officer and Vice President Patient Care Services with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Nursing Practice, Healthcare Performance Improvement, Regulatory Compliance, Physician Relations, and Healthcare Quality Management. Strong healthcare services professional with a Master's degree focused in Health/Health Care Administration/Management from Ohio University.

Experience

Banner Health

Western Division CNO & CNO North Colorado Medical Center July 2019 - Present (1 year 1 month)

Northern Colorado

Mercy Health

3 years 9 months

Regional Chief Nursing Officer & VP Patient Care Services June 2017 - July 2019 (2 years 2 months)

Springfield Region

Interim VP Patient Care Services and CNO December 2016 - June 2017 (7 months)

Springfield, Ohio

Chief Quality Officer and Patient Safety Officer November 2015 - June 2017 (1 year 8 months)

Springfield, Ohio

Adena Health System

8 years 2 months

System Director of Quality and Medical Staff Services November 2012 - October 2015 (3 years)

Chillicothe, OH

I am responsible for clinical quality performance system-wide. This role provides oversight to Quality, Performance Improvement, Infection Prevention, Patient Safety, Accreditation and Medical Staff Services, including Physician Credentialing and Physician Peer Review.

Director of Accreditation November 2011 - May 2013 (1 year 7 months) Adena Health System

Infection Prevention /Quality Resource Specialist June 2008 - November 2011 (3 years 6 months) Adena Health System

Registered Nurse September 2007 - May 2009 (1 year 9 months) Adena Health System

Mercy Health System
Registered Nurse
March 2005 - August 2007 (2 years 6 months)
Cincinnati, Ohio

Highland District Hospital Registered Nurse May 2001 - March 2005 (3 years 11 months)

Education

Ohio University

Master's degree, Health/Health Care Administration/

Management · (2012 - 2014)

Ohio University
Bachelors degree, Nursing Science (2009 - 2011)

Southern State Community College
Associate's degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (1999 - 2001)